<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="manualtitle">Instruction manual</string>
    <string name="manualcontent">There are five buttons and one slider to control the car. \nThe four buttons with arrow symbols are used to control the direction of your vehicle. \nThe stop button in the center can be used to immediately stop the vehicle. \nThe slider on the right can be used to control the speed of the vehicle. \nWe hope that you have a lot of fun in the Esstelleague!</string>
    <string name="darkthemetitle">Dark theme</string>
    <string name="hintstitle">Hints</string>
    <string name="soundtitle">Sound</string>
    <string name="languagetitle">Language</string>
    <string name="aboutustitle">About us</string>
    <string name="ca_fastHint">The slider controls the speed</string>
    <string name="daa_playat">Play at</string>
    <string name="ca_selectvehicle">First pick your fairy tale mobile</string>
    <string name="mqtt_connect">Connecting...</string>
    <string name="mqtt_connect_error">Failed to connect</string>
    <string name="mqtt_connect_suc">Connected</string>
    <string name="aboutuscontent" translatable="false">"We are a studentteam employed by the Essteling. We are building the application Essteling, made to make waiting in the queue slightly more interesting. "</string>
    <string name="neem_controle_over_1_van_onze_sprookjes_auto_s_en_bepaal_hoe_het_verhaal_zich_verder_afspeel_in_dit_interactieve_autospel" translatable="false">Take control of 1 of our fairy tale cars and determine how the story continues in this interactive car game.</string>
    <string name="nieuws">News</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="rv_baron">To enter the mine, Baron 1898 lets you fall 37.5 meters down! Quick, try to get the gold in the underground corridor before the White Wieven sabotage your chance of wealth to ride this dive coaster.</string>
    <string name="rv_bob">With a speed of 60 km / h down? Swing through curves and feel the wind sliding past your face. In the bobsleigh track you shiver even without snow. The Bob is a 524 m long bob track and suitable for all daredevils. In principle everyone is allowed in this attraction, but children under 1.20 m must be accompanied by an adult and this attraction is not suitable for pregnant women. For people who only dare in this attraction there is a special \'single rider queue\'. The bob track is open if the weather permits.</string>
    <string name="rv_dezwevendebelg">Despite bad weather conditions, captain Seppe van der Decken sailed with his ship De Zwevende Belg, in search of wealth. His greed was so great that he ordered his crew to sail on Easter Sunday, even though it was forbidden. Since then, everyone on board has been doomed to sail forever on the seven seas. To this day, the ship with its bright red sails is seen everywhere in the world ... It is now called De Zwevende Belg!</string>
    <string name="rv_droomvlucht">Unicorns and forest animals come to life in this enchanting world. And when night falls, the cities float weightlessly through the darkness. Until the daylight returns and everyone in the enchanting forest wakes up happily again in this indoor attraction Dream Flight.</string>
    <string name="rv_fatamorgana">A magnificent treasure is hidden deep in the Eastern Palace. And while the sultan surrounds himself with splendor, the dark prisons fill with criminals and rats. Spend some time on the water and view all kinds of Eastern scenes. A boat takes you through neighborhoods full of poverty but also wealth. And a giant protects the most valuable possession of the sultan: his gems, silver candlesticks and gold pieces.</string>
    <string name="rv_festivaloveral">Share joy and happiness with each other and meet happy people. Jokie and Jet take you on a journey to different countries! Get to know different cultures and party with all the red noses in the world. Discover the differences and similarities in Festival Everywhere.</string>
    <string name="rv_johanendeeenhoorn">Defeat the unicorn that is ravaging the kingdom. All warriors are challenged to choose one of the courses and to beat the beast with \"Water\" or \"Fire\". The one who succeeds the fastest, gets all the honor after a ride in this wooden racing roller coaster.</string>
    <string name="rv_monsieurcannibale">On the island of Monsieur Cannibale, large boiling kettles constantly revolve above a crackling fire. Anyone who sets foot on land can take a seat in this dizzying adventure until she begs the cannibal for mercy. You and the whole family are invited to take a seat in Monsieur Cannibale’s cooking pots. Even when it rains, the fire from this indoor attraction will be alight.</string>
    <string name="rv_python">escape the rotating stranglehold of the Python that is waiting for you in peace. Survive the winding movements at great heights in this steel roller coaster with double loop and corkscrew.</string>
    <string name="rv_symbolica">Experience the covered family attraction Symbolica, an enchanting palace where fantasy comes to life. Go on an audience with the king. Tovernar Pardoes ensures that every visit is surprising and enchanting. Wander through the secret corridors and magical rooms and fall from one surprise to the other.</string>
    <string name="rv_vogelrok">Vogel Skirt takes you along! You experience a hair-raising flight in the dark in its claws. Along snakes through the darkness until the enormous bird of prey with the power of a hundred lions has reached its nest. Experience the adventure just like Sinbad the Zeeman.</string>
</resources>